question_data = [ 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in "
                                                  "other languages.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress"
                                                  " partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the "
                                                  "referendum from September 2014.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanks giving",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]

